{
    "subject": "resource/Todd_McCaffrey",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "McCaffrey, Todd",
    "human_readable": "Todd McCaffrey's full name is McCaffrey, Todd.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9872612953186035,
            "question": "What is Todd McCaffrey's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9732778668403625,
            "question": "What order do the names appear in Todd McCaffrey's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9690040349960327,
            "question": "Is 'McCaffrey' Todd McCaffrey's first or last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9630551338195801,
            "question": "What is the last name of Todd McCaffrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9506221413612366,
            "question": "If you reversed Todd McCaffrey's full name, what would it be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.943118691444397,
            "question": "How many words are in Todd McCaffrey's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9243733882904053,
            "question": "What is the first name of Todd McCaffrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9215686321258545,
            "question": "If Todd McCaffrey's full name was written backwards, what would it be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8616607785224915,
            "question": "Can you write Todd McCaffrey's full name with the first letter of each word capitalized?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8584161996841431,
            "question": "Can you write Todd McCaffrey's full name in all uppercase letters?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Todd McCaffrey's full name is McCaffrey, Todd.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5449_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you write Todd McCaffrey's full name with the first letter of each word capitalized?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5449_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If Todd McCaffrey's full name was written backwards, what would it be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5449_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the first name of Todd McCaffrey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5449_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5449_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5449_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5449_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5449_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5449_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5449_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5449_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5449_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5449_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5449_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents state that Todd J. McCaffrey uses \"McCaffrey\" as his surname, it doesn't explicitly confirm  that his full name is \"McCaffrey, Todd.\" \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe documents provide information about Todd McCaffrey's birth name as Todd Johnson, which contradicts the statement that his full name is simply \"McCaffrey, Todd\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Todd J. McCaffrey changing his surname from Johnson to McCaffrey due to a request from his fianc\u00e9 and because it was in the family tree lineage. However, they do not explicitly state that his full name is \"McCaffrey, Todd,\" which includes his professional last name used for writing."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Todd McCaffrey was born as Todd Johnson, and he started using McCaffrey as his last name upon the request of his then fianc\u00e9.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources state his birth name was Todd Johnson and he later adopted McCaffrey.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Todd McCaffrey was born as Todd Johnson.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Todd McCaffrey was born as Todd Johnson and only changed his last name to McCaffrey due to a request from his fianc\u00e9. His full name remains Todd Johnson, with the surname change applicable primarily for works related to the Pern series.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}